Art Buchwald Papers
Manuscript Division, Library of Congress
- Personal File, 1885-2007 (Box 192-222)
  - Health (Box 213)
    - Kidney stones, Project Buchwald, 1975-1976 (Box 213)
    - Medical files, 1977-2006, undated, (2 folders) (Box 213)
    - Prosthetic leg, circa 2006 See Container OV 12, same heading (Box 213)
  - Identification documents (Box 213)
    - French residency cards, Ann and Art, 1957 (Box 213)
    - Passports (Box 213)
      - Buchwald, Ann and Connie, 1952-1976 (Box 213)
      - Buchwald, Art, 1948-1960, 1982-1997, undated (Box 214)
    - Press passes and credentials, 1949-1984, undated (Box 214)
  - Jury duty, 2001 (Box 214)
  - Oral histories (Box 214)
    - The American Jewish Committee, 1976-1978, (4 folders) (Box 214)
    - Buchwald, Art, undated (Box 214)
    - Burnstein, David and Julie, 2006 Aug. 21, mss86197_178_017
    - Correspondence, 1987 (Box 214)
    - Expenses, 1991 (Box 214)
    - Goldberg, Harriet and George, 2003 Sept. 7, mss86197_178_231
    - Gordon, Alice, 1991 (Box 215)
    - Gordon, Alice and Edith Jaffe, 1991-1992, (2 folders) (Box 215)
    - John F. Kennedy Library, Boston, Mass., 1969-1973, 1990-1991 (Box 215)
    - Lampner, Eddie, 1991 (Box 215)
    - Leaving Home memoir, 1961, 1991-1994, undated, (2 folders) (Box 215)
    - Questions, undated (Box 215)
    - Valenti, Jack, and Art Buchwald, 2006, mss86197_178_014
  - Outgoing mail and stamp usage log, 1977-1981 (Box 215)
  - Paris years (Box 215)
    - Bull Moose Party, 1952, 1957-1960, 1974, undated See also Container OV 7, Posters (Box 215)
    - Chinatown Restaurant business files, 1962-1972, (2 folders) (Box 215)
    - Chinatown Restaurant business files, 1962-1972, (1 folder) (Box 216)
    - Diary, 1959 (Box 216)
    - Drive to Moscow, circa 1958 (Box 216)
    - Early writings, 1948, undated (Box 216)
    - French-language flashcards and notebook, circa 1949-circa 1960 (Box 216)
    - Miscellany, undated (Box 216)
    - New York Herald Tribune (Box 216)
      - Article drafts, circa 1949-circa 1960 (Box 216)
      - Correspondence, 1949-1960, (3 folders) (Box 216)
      - Miscellany, 1953, undated (Box 216)
    - Notes on writing process, circa 1957 (Box 216)
    - Printed ephemera, (2 folders) (Box 216)
      - 1940-1953, (1 folder) (Box 216)
      - 1955-1962, undated, (1 folder); See also Container OV 7, Opera program (Box 217)
    - Prix de la Bonne Humeur (French humor award), 1958 (Box 217)
    - Receipts and bills (Box 217)
      - American National Interests Commissary, 1955-1962 (Box 217)
      - Family dog pedigree, 1953 (Box 217)
      - Gas and electricity, 1956-1961, (2 folders) (Box 217)
      - Heat, 1956-1961 (Box 217)
      - Household, 1955-1962, (2 folders) (Box 217)
      - Medical, 1948, 1956-1962 (Box 217)
      - Miscellaneous, 1952-1962 (Box 217)
      - Rent, 1957-1961 (Box 217)
      - Salary, 1949 (Box 217)
      - Securité sociale and allocations familiales, 1956-1963 (Box 217)
      - Taxes and insurance, 1952-1962 (Box 218)
      - Telephone, 1958-1962 (Box 218)
      - Warranties and guarantees, 1958-1961, undated (Box 218)
    - Restaurants (Box 218)
      - List, undated (Box 218)
      - Menus, 1953-1959 See also Container OV 7, same heading (Box 218)
      - Where Paris Dines by Julian Street, 1929, 1949 (Box 218)
    - Return to United States (Box 218)
      - Artwork appraisal, 1962 (Box 218)
      - House inventory, 1956-1965, undated (Box 218)
    - Running of the bulls, 1958, 1995 See also Container OV 7, Posters (Box 218)
    - Voyage to France, 1948 (Box 218)
  - Parties and celebrations (Box 218)
    - 60th birthday, 1985 See Container OV 11, Los Angeles Times front page (Box 218)
    - 80th birthday party, 2005, (4 folders) (Box 219)
      - Photographs, mss86197_178_001; mss86197_178_004
      - Video files, mss86197_178_226
    - Christmas gifts, 1990-1993, 2001 (Box 219)
    - Dinner party for Dinah Shore, 1983 (Box 219)
    - Dinner party for John Lindsay, 1966 (Box 219)
    - Easter, 1983-1984, (2 folders) (Box 219)
    - Inscribed menus, 1968, 2002 (Box 219)
    - Invitation lists, undated (Box 219)
  - United States Marine Corps (Box 219)
    - Certification cards, 1944-1945 (Box 219)
    - Clippings and printed ephemera, 1945 (Box 219)
    - Correspondence, 1945 (Box 219)
    - Discharge documents, 1945-1946, undated (Box 219)
    - G.I. Bill documents, 1945-1948 (Box 219)
    - Holiday dinner menus, 1943 (Box 219)
    - Photographs, 1939-1945, undated See Container OV 7, Enlistment photograph, (1 folder) (Box 219)
    - Photographs, 1939-1945, undated, (1 folder) (Box 220)
    - Service ribbons and first aid kit items, 1942-1947 See Container OV 5, Service ribbons and items from a soldier's first aid kit (Box 220)
    - Writings (Box 220)
      - "The Coral Courier," 1944 (Box 220)
      - Letters to the editor, 1942-1944 (Box 220)
      - "Jumper Journal," 1948-1990 (Box 220)
      - "The U-Man Comedy," 1943-1944, 1964 (Box 220)
  - University of Southern California, Los Angeles, Calif. (Box 220)
    - Academic writings, 1946-1948, (4 folders) (Box 220)
    - Aptitude test, 1946 (Box 220)
    - Art Buchwald Advertising Agency, undated (Box 220)
    - Clippings, 1946-1947 (Box 220)
    - Correspondence, 1946-1948 (Box 221)
    - Daily Trojan articles, 1947-1948 (Box 221)
    - Drivers license and cards with cardholder, 1948 (Box 221)
    - Miscellany, undated (Box 221)
    - Photographs, circa 1939-circa 1948 (Box 221)
    - Summer employment, 1946 (Box 221)
    - WAMPUS (Box 221)
      - Issues, 1947-1948 (Box 221)
      - Miscellany, 1947-1949 (Box 221)
      - Photographs, 1947-1949 (Box 221)
    - Yearbooks (Box 221)
      - 1946, (1 folder) (Box 221)
      - 1948, (1 folder) (Box 222)
- Subject File, 1952-2006 (Box 222-236)
  The Subject File holds a wide range of files pertaining to Buchwald’s personal interests, organizations and charities he supported, and organizations in which he was involved, among other topics. Buchwald’s many charitable contributions are documented in this series and include scholarships he funded, undergraduate students he sponsored, monetary donations to nonprofit organizations, prizes he donated for charitable auctions, which was usually the right to name a character in one of his upcoming columns, and his service as the auctioneer for the annual Possible Dreams auction in Martha’s Vineyard. Many humor conferences and organizations are represented in this series and include material regarding an exchange of American and Soviet humorists in 1988, for which Buchwald traveled to the Soviet Union. Letters from readers are included in the Subject File and record reactions to some of Buchwald’s columns. Correspondence and printed matter chronicle Buchwald’s ongoing relationships with the New York Herald Tribune, United States Marine Corps, and University of Southern California. Researchers should consult the Personal File for material more directly related to Buchwald’s early career with the New York Herald Tribune while in Paris, France, his service as a Marine, and his tenure as a student at the University of Southern California.
  Material types include brochures, correspondence, newspaper clippings, programs, and printed matter.
  Arranged alphabetically by topic or material type.
  - Alexander Graham Bell Association for the Deaf, 1979-1988 (Box 222)
  - American Academy and Institute of Arts and Letters, 1986-1988, 1997-2001, (5 folders) (Box 222)
  - American Civil Liberties Union, 1978-1979 (Box 223)
  - American News Women's Club, 1988 (Box 223)
  - Amnesty International, 1976-1983 (Box 223)
  - Apollo 11 launch and moon landing, 1969 (Box 223)
  - Association for Advancement of the Mentally Handicapped, 1983 (Box 223)
  - Boards and committees, 1984-2004, (3 folders) (Box 223)
  - Califano, Joseph A., Jr., delegation to Shanghai, China, 1979-1980, (2 folders) (Box 223)
  - Charitable contributions (Box 223)
    - 1984-1986, (2 folders) (Box 223)
    - 1987-2001, (5 folders) (Box 224)
  - Chess, 1970-2000 (Box 224)
  - Coca-Cola Company, 1987-1988 (Box 224)
  - Colby, William Egan, interview, ABC News 20/20, 1979 May 27, (2 folders) (Box 224)
  - Colleges and universities (Box 225)
    - Georgetown University, Washington, D.C., 1978-1984, (2 folders) (Box 225)
    - Harvard University, Cambridge, Mass., 1992 (Box 225)
    - University of Notre Dame, Notre Dame, Ind., 1988-1993 (Box 225)
  - Depression, 1990-2005 (Box 225)
  - Donated auction items, 1997-2002, (4 folders) (Box 225)
  - Editorial cartoons, 1953-1997 (Box 225)
  - Energy, 1977 (Box 225)
  - Fitness, 1985-1987 (Box 225)
  - Foster care and orphanages, 1959, 1977-2001 (Box 226)
  - Freedom of Information Act requests, 1975 (Box 226)
  - Friends of Westminster Cathedral, London, England, 1978-1981 (Box 226)
  - Horse named "Art Buchwald," 1992 (Box 226)
  - Humor conferences and organizations (Box 226)
    - American Academy of Humor, 1975 (Box 226)
    - American Humor (newsletter), 1980-1983 (Box 226)
    - American-Soviet Cultural Exchange of Humorists, Soviet Union, 1988, (2 folders) (Box 226)
    - Erma Bombeck Conference on Popular American Humor, University of Dayton, Dayton, Oh., 1999-2000 (Box 226)
    - International Colloquia on Jewish Humor, 1984-1986 (Box 226)
    - Western Humor and Irony Membership (WHIM) conferences, 1981-1984 (Box 226)
    - Workshop Library on World Humour, 1977-1987 (Box 226)
  - Invitations and programs (Box 226)
    - 1964-1966, (1 folder) (Box 226)
    - 1970-2002, (3 folders) (Box 227)
  - Jokes (miscellaneous), 1984-2004 (Box 227)
  - Kennedy Center, Washington, D.C., 1964, 1971-1976 (Box 227)
  - Kennedy Center Honors (Box 227)
    - 1978-1981, (3 folders) (Box 227)
    - 1983-1990, (3 folders) (Box 228)
  - Laughter as medicine, 1983 (Box 228)
  - Letters from readers (Box 228)
    - "Fine Arts Committee" column, 1962 (Box 228)
    - Hate mail, 1962-1995, (2 folders) (Box 228)
    - Kase, Keith (inmate, Texas Department of Corrections), 1961-1968 (Box 228)
    - Killen, William L. (inmate, Philadelphia, Pa., prison), 1981-1982 (Box 228)
    - Malefyt, Mary, 1969-1970, (2 folders) (Box 228)
    - Non-drinkers column, 1962 (Box 228)
    - Nuclear War columns, 1983 (Box 228)
    - Prayer in schools column, 1984 (Box 228)
    - Public restrooms column, 1980, (1 folder) (Box 228)
    - Public restrooms column, 1980, (1 folder) (Box 229)
    - Request for secretary responses, 1998 (Box 229)
    - Sexual abuse column, 2002 (Box 229)
    - "Stork control" (birth control) column, 1984 (Box 229)
    - Unwanted babies, "Senator Beenbag" column, 1982 (Box 229)
  - London Library, London, England, 1980-1981 (Box 229)
  - Martha's Vineyard, Mass. (Box 229)
    - 1975-1990, (7 folders) (Box 229)
    - 1991-2001, (8 folders) (Box 230)
    - 2003-2005, undated, (4 folders) (Box 231)
  - National Kidney Foundation and kidneys (general), 1976-1992 (Box 231)
  - National Rifle Association of America and guns (general), 1967-1990 (Box 231)
  - New York Herald Tribune (Box 231)
    - Centennial celebration, 1986-1987, (3 folders) (Box 231)
    - Column cancellation, 2003 (Box 231)
    - Correspondence (Box 231)
      - 1963-1981, (1 folder) (Box 231)
      - 1984-2006, (1 folder) (Box 232)
    - What's Going On? In and around the New York Herald Tribune (newsletter), 1952-1954 (Box 232)
  - Nuclear warfare, civil defense, 1981-1983 (Box 232)
  - Office space leases, 1994-1997 (Box 232)
  - PEN American Center (nonprofit organization), 1986-1988 (Box 232)
  - Salomon Brothers, 1981 (Box 232)
  - Scholarships (Box 232)
    - Art Buchwald Scholarship, University of Southern California, School of Journalism, Los Angeles, Calif., 1985-2006, (3 folders) (Box 232)
    - Correspondence, 1982-2006, (2 folders) (Box 232)
    - Smith, Deirdre, 1991-1995 (Box 232)
  - Soviet Union, 1955, 1978, 1985-1993 (Box 233)
  - Special Approaches to Juvenile Assistance, Inc., 1973-1981 (Box 233)
  - Telemarketing calls, 1987-1990 (Box 233)
  - Tennis (Box 233)
    - General, 1971-1988, (2 folders) (Box 233)
    - Robert F. Kennedy Pro-Celebrity Tennis Tournament, 1970-1980, (2 folders) (Box 233)
    - Saturday Night Massacre Tennis Party, 1975-1979 (Box 233)
  - United Service Organizations (USO), 1967-1968 (Box 233)
  - United States Air Force, 1965, 1975 (Box 233)
  - United States Marine Corps (Box 233)
    - Correspondence (Box 233)
      - 1978-1984, (1 folder) (Box 233)
      - 1985-2002, (6 folders) (Box 234)
    - Enewetak Atoll, Marshall Islands, 1977-1980 (Box 234)
    - Ephemera, undated (Box 234)
    - Evening parade in honor of Buchwald, 1999, (3 folders) (Box 234)
    - Joint Services Officers' Wives' Club, 1977 (Box 234)
    - Names and addresses, 1989-2001 (Box 234)
    - National Museum of American Jewish Military History, Washington, D.C., 1994-1995 (Box 234)
    - Photographs, 1990-2006, undated, (6 folders) (Box 235)
    - Printed matter, 1958-1991, (2 folders) (Box 235)
    - "Proud Warriors: The Jewish Experience in the U.S. Marine Corps," 2000 (Box 235)
    - Writings, 1984-1990 (Box 235)
  - University of Southern California, Los Angeles, Calif. (Box 235)
    - 1969-1995, (4 folders) (Box 235)
    - 2000-2005, (1 folder) (Box 236)
  - Video and film, 1984 (Box 236)
  - World's Fair, New York, N.Y., 1964 (Box 236)
- Digital File, 1987-2006 (Box DF)
  The Digital File series contains the contents of a personal computer and word-processing disks created and used by Buchwald between 1987 and 2006. The series documents his professional activities during this period and focuses primarily on speech and column drafts, though to a lesser extent, correspondence and photographs are also represented. The file structure of the digital content has been maintained as received and Buchwald’s word-processing files were saved in no particular chronological or topical order, resulting in a mix of date ranges, subjects, and document types across digital ID numbers. In general, speeches and columns found on disks range in date from 1987 to 1996, while those found on Buchwald’s personal computer range in date from 2002 to 2006. An inventory of some of the disks was created, presumably by one of Buchwald's assistants, and a PDF copy is appended to the finding aid as Appendix B. Correspondence was saved among column and speech drafts and dates between 1987 and 1996. In an effort to ensure correspondence was not overlooked among the digital files, digital ID numbers containing letters are listed under “Correspondence” and under “Columns and speeches.” Correspondence found in the Digital File series includes several letters Buchwald wrote to his wife, Ann, during their separation and her cancer treatments. Letters from Buchwald to his children and friends are also found in this series. In other instances where digital materials were found with the collection’s paper content, the digital materials are listed and described alongside the paper records.
  Material types include book manuscripts, correspondence, photographs, and speech and column drafts.
  Arranged alphabetically by material type and listed by digital ID number thereunder, with the file structure of the digital content maintained as received.
  - Correspondence
    - 1987, mss86197_178_109
    - 1988, mss86197_178_172
    - 1989, mss86197_178_145; mss86197_178_179
    - 1990, mss86197_178_054; mss86197_178_167; mss86197_178_168
    - 1991, mss86197_178_175
    - 1991-1994, mss86197_178_063
    - 1992, mss86197_178_029; mss86197_178_059; mss86197_178_061; mss86197_178_065; mss86197_178_116; mss86197_178_123; mss86197_178_129; mss86197_178_182
    - 1992-1994, mss86197_178_031; mss86197_178_066; mss86197_178_181
    - 1993, mss86197_178_035; mss86197_178_036; mss86197_178_044; mss86197_178_060; mss86197_178_068; mss86197_178_084; mss86197_178_117
    - 1995, mss86197_178_100
    - 1996, mss86197_178_099
  - Writings
    - Columns only
      - 1988, mss86197_178_146
      - 1989, mss86197_178_145
      - 1991-1993, mss86197_178_061; mss86197_178_063; mss86197_178_123; mss86197_178_132
      - 1992, mss86197_178_087; mss86197_178_124
      - 1992-1996, mss86197_178_029; mss86197_178_059; mss86197_178_066; mss86197_178_150
      - 1993, mss86197_178_104; mss86197_178_126
      - 1993-1995, mss86197_178_051; mss86197_178_136
      - 1994, mss86197_178_050; mss86197_178_106
      - 1995, mss86197_178_032; mss86197_178_033; mss86197_178_100; mss86197_178_140
      - 1996, mss86197_178_072; mss86197_178_105
    - Speeches only
      - 1989-1991, mss86197_178_169
      - 1991, mss86197_178_002
      - 1993, mss86197_178_138
      - 1995, mss86197_178_108
    - Speeches and columns mixed
      - 1987, mss86197_178_109; mss86197_178_118
      - 1987-1991, mss86197_178_180
      - 1989-1991, mss86197_178_170; mss86197_178_179
      - 1990-1993, mss86197_178_054; mss86197_178_084
      - 1991, mss86197_178_166; mss86197_178_168; mss86197_178_171; mss86197_178_172; mss86197_178_175; mss86197_178_176; mss86197_178_177; mss86197_178_178
      - 1991-1993, mss86197_178_044; mss86197_178_165; mss86197_178_167; mss86197_178_173; mss86197_178_174
      - 1992, mss86197_178_065; mss86197_178_107; mss86197_178_116; mss86197_178_134; mss86197_178_181; mss86197_178_182
      - 1992-1994, mss86197_178_031; mss86197_178_036; mss86197_178_049; mss86197_178_052; mss86197_178_060; mss86197_178_062; mss86197_178_122; mss86197_178_164; mss86197_178_194
      - 1993, mss86197_178_068; mss86197_178_141
      - 1993-1996, mss86197_178_035; mss86197_178_117; mss86197_178_131
      - 1994-1995, mss86197_178_038; mss86197_178_042
      - 1995-1996, mss86197_178_099
      - 1996, mss86197_178_092
  - iBook laptop computer (Closed), mss86197_178_200; The contents of Buchwald's laptop are currently unavailable.
    - Writing files, 2002-2006
    - Photographs, 2001-2005
- Oversize, 1925-2007 (Box OV 1-OV 18)
  Oversize and unusually formatted material feature a commemorative cigar associated with Buchwald's radio program Buchwald On, a crank toy in the form of Buchwald at a book signing for his memoir, Leaving Home, the prosthetic leg Buchwald wore after his leg was amputated in 2006, and many promotional posters associated with Buchwald's columns and books. Other material includes storyboards, photographs, drawings, speech cards, and scrapbooks.
  Listed and described according to the series, containers, and folders from which the material was removed. Physically grouped and housed by size of the items, with containers numbered sequentially according to the physical arrangement.
  - General Correspondence
    - VIP
      - Letter, "Irving Hoffman's Handy Nervous Breakdown Avoider and Mail Answering Form," 1964 (Container 5, Hoffman, Irving) (Box OV 7)
      - Photograph and Valentine card to Buchwald from Ethel Kennedy (Container 5, Kennedy, Ethel)
        - Photograph of Ethel Kennedy inscribed “For mad, gay loveable, devil-may-care Art. With love, Ethel,” 1965 (Box OV 7)
        - Valentine card in the shape of a heart from Ethel Kennedy, 1969 (Box OV 10)
      - Two photographs of Buchwald with Eunice Kennedy Shriver, 1989, undated (Container 7, Shriver, Eunice Kennedy) (Box OV 7)
    - Chronological
      - Scrapbook inviting Buchwald to participate in a documentary titled “A Matter of Faith,” 1970 (Container 27, 1970) (Box OV 8)
  - Writings
    - Books
      - Drawings inspired by The Bollo Caper made by students, 1975 June (Container 52, Letters and drawings from Children) (Box OV 7)
      - Photograph collage of Buchwald from the cover shoot of I Think I Don't Remember, 1987 (Container 56, Publicity packet) (Box OV 17)
    - Columns
      - Linen print of "Prayer for Tourists," undated (Container 65, "Prayer for Tourists") (Box OV 10)
    - Memoirs
      - Crank toy in the form of Buchwald as a Marine and as an author at a book signing for Leaving Home, 1994 (Container 127, Publicity and book parties) (Box OV 13)
    - Plays and screenplays
      - Sheep on the Runway
        - Poster advertising Sheep on the Runway, National Theatre, Washington, D.C., circa 1970 May (Container 131, Publicity) (Box OV 10)
        - Scrapbook containing programs, ticket stubs, clippings, and notes of congratulations, 1970 (Container 131, Scrapbook) (Box OV 8)
  - Buchwald v. Paramount Pictures Corp.
    - Scrapbook containing clippings and notes related to the lawsuit, circa 1990 (Container 137, circa 1990) (Box OV 9)
  - Administrative File
    - Production projects
      - Cigar with custom Buchwald On: The Art Buchwald Radio Program wrapper, circa 1969 (Container 159, Miscellany) (Box OV 1)
      - Storyboard illustrations for “Art Buchwald’s Pro-Football Murder Mystery,” created by Bill Melendez Productions, Inc., circa 1969-1976 (Container 160, Bill Melendez Productions, Inc.) (Box OV 10)
      - Animation celluloids featuring Buchwald, circa 1979 (Container 161, Richard Williams, Ltd., Washington Post advertisement) (Box OV 7)
      - Poster advertisement for The Art of Living play production at the Criterion Theatre, London, England, 1960 (Container 161, The Art of Living, Oscar Lewenstein, Ltd., and Donmar Productions, Ltd.) (Box OV 10)
    - Publicity
      - Newsday Magazine featuring article titled “Art Buchwald: Memories of a Hollis Boy," 1984, Apr. 22 (Container 168, Magazine covers) (Box OV 7)
      - Promotional posters advertising many of Buchwald's book publications, circa 1950-circa 1994 (Container 168, Books)
        - Promotional posters for several of Buchwald’s publications (Box OV 10)
        - Promotional poster for You Can Fool All of the People All of the Time (Box OV 17)
      - Promotional posters and newspaper advertisements for Buchwald's syndicated column (Container 168, Columns)
        - Advertisements appearing in various newspapers and one Washington Post poster advertisement, 1955-1982 (Box OV 11)
        - Herald Tribune poster advertisement - “Buchwald Goes to Washington,” 1962 Sept. (Box OV 18)
    - Publishing
      - Poster advertisement for Buchwald’s syndicated column and his book, I Think I Don’t Remember, 1987 (Container 171, Los Angeles Times Syndicate) (Box OV 11)
      - Poster advertisement celebrating Buchwald’s twentieth anniversary with the Los Angeles Times Syndicate, 1993 (Container 172, Los Angeles Times Syndicate) (Box OV 11)
  - Speeches
    - Chronological file
      - Poster advertising Buchwald lecture at Massachusetts Institute of Technology, Cambridge, Mass., 1975, Nov. 10 (Container 189, 1975) (Box OV 11)
      - Dinner napkin bearing illustration of Buchwald and inscription by LeRoy Neiman, 1979, Jan. 11 (Container 189, 1979) (Box OV 10)
    - Speech cards (Container 192, Same title)
      - Alphabetical by speech title, undated (Box OV 2)
      - Alphabetical by subject, undated (Box OV 3)
      - Speech fragments, undated (Box OV 4)
      - Miscellaneous speeches, undated (Box OV 6)
  - Personal
    - Photographs and signatures from Army and Navy Neurosurgeons, circa 1980s (Container 201, Miscellany) (Box OV 17)
    - Paintings of miscellaneous subjects and origin, 1959, undated (Container 201, Paintings) (Box OV 11)
    - Award from Ethel Kennedy, 1978, Sept. 13 (Container 203, Joke awards) (Box OV 7)
    - Award from Vineyard Haven Yacht Club Members, 1992 Sept. 5 (Container 203, Joke awards) (Box OV 17)
    - Boston American newspaper from day of Buchwald's birth, 1925 Oct. 20 (Container 205, Newspapers from day of birth) (Box OV 11)
    - Scrapbooks created for Buchwald’s memorial service, 2007 (Container 206, Scrapbooks)
      - Vol. I (Box OV 14 a-b)
      - Vol. II (Box OV 15 a-c)
      - Vol. III (Box OV 16 a-b)
    - Promotional poster Ann Buchwald's memoir, Seems Like Yesterday, circa 1980 (Container 211, Publicity) (Box OV 11)
    - Card made by Art Buchwald for Ann Buchwald for their seventh wedding anniversary, 1959 (Container 213, Wedding anniversaries) (Box OV 7)